Historic New England
Bowen family papers
During the 2013-2014 collection reprocessing/updating, the 1983 arrangement scheme was updated; most of the original folder titles were maintained (appropriate headings and folder titles were supplied, as applicable); discrepancies between actual folder titles and the original 1983 finding aid were corrected; related folders were combined or rearranged, as applicable; the accumulated unprocessed material (prior to 2005) was incorporated into the collection; scope and content notes were updated to reflect the changes; and additional research was added to the biographical/historical sketch and genealogy. Preservation issues were identified and basic preservation methods were applied, as applicable; rusted, loose, and otherwise dangerous fasteners (i.e., paperclips, staples, pins, etc.) were removed, as applicable; fragile and vulnerable materials (i.e., acidic material; adhesive tape; fragments; clippings and newsprint; small and loose items; weak and/or damaged materials; etc.) were noted and preservation photocopies and/or enclosures were made for the materials (or materials were interleafed within file boxes), as applicable; papers throughout the collection were removed from envelopes (if applicable), unfolded, flattened, and related pages were noted with corresponding information in brackets ([x-1/3], [x-2/3], [x-3/3]; and objects, oversize material, and photographic material were rehoused appropriately (or materials were interleafed within file boxes), as applicable. The collection was rehoused (in acid-free folders and boxes), numbered, labeled, barcoded, and stored accordingly; subsequent accessions were tracked and noted with their corresponding items; missing items were noted; and related collections held by Historic New England and other repositories were researched and noted. The original 1983 paper document finding aid was updated to be DACS-compliant, as applicable; converted into an electronic 2010-2013 Microsoft Word document finding aid (with corresponding paper finding aid); and entered into the collection record in the MINISIS M2A online database.
2013 extent of collection (prior to updating): 3 cartons (letter-wise)= 3.75 linear feet; 12 file boxes (legal-size)= 5.01 linear feet; 02 file boxes (letter-size)= 0.83 linear feet; 2 multi-purpose boxes; Vertical files/flat files. Note: Yale linear footage calculator: approximately 9.59 linear feet (3 cartons, 14 file boxes), plus 2 multi-purpose boxes and vertical files.
Indexing Terms
Aspinwall, Peter; Aspinwall, William; Atwell, George Benjamin; Atwell, Mary Meekem (Tennent); Barney, Hiram; Barney, Edward A.; Barney, Susan E. (Tappan); Beecher, Henry Ward, 1813-1887; Bowen, Augusta Floyd (Vingut); Bowen, Carolyn Mae (Clegg), 1877-1949; Bowen, Clarence Winthrop, 1852-1935; Bowen, Edward A., 1847-1926; Bowen, Edward Eaton, 1815-1887; Bowen, Elizabeth White (Plummer), 1848-1922; Bowen, Ellen (Holt), 1834-1903; Bowen, Emily Vivian (Hyde), 1869-1925; Bowen, Ethel Plummer, 1879-; Bowen, Francis; Bowen, Franklin Davis, 1860-1940; Bowen, George, 1789-1846; Bowen, Henry; Bowen, Henry Chandler, 1813-1896; Bowen, Henry Elliot, 1845-1919; Bowen, Herbert Wolcott, 1856-1927; Bowen, John Eliot, 1858-1890; Bowen, Lucy Maria (Tappan), 1825-1863; Bowen, Lydia Wolcott (Eaton), 1793-1864; Bowen, Margaret (Davis); Bowen, Mary (Chandler), 1760-1834; Bowen, Mary (Dana), 1727-1813; Bowen, Matthew, 1724-1806; Bowen, Paul Holt, 1868-1895; Bowen, Pauline, 1895-; Bowen, Roxana Atwater (Wentworth), 1854-1935; Bowen, Sophronia Tennent (Atwell), 1818-1899; Bowen, William, 1763-1837; Browning, Elizabeth Barrett, 1806-1861; Chamberlin, Lewis; Chandler, Eleanor "Nellie"; Chandler, Frances; Chandler, Mary (Hodges); Chandler, Peter; Dana, Isaac; Dana, Sarah (Winchester); Dexter, Samuel; Eaton, Edwin; Eaton, Eliot; Eaton, Elizabeth (Davis); Franklin, Benjamin, 1706-1790; Fremont, John Charles, 1813-1890; Grenfell, Wilfred; Hardy, Arthur Sherburne, 1847-1930; Hardy, Grace Aspinwall (Bowen), 1850-1940; Harrison, Benjamin, 1833-1901; Holt, Alexina C.; Holt, Constance, 1879-1968; Holt, George C. (George Chandler), 1843-1931; Holt, Hamilton, 1872-1951; Holt, Henry Chandler, 1881-1955; Holt, Hiram; Holt, Mary (Chandler); Holt, Mary Louisa (Bowen), 1848-1925; Holt, Stuart, 1876-1900; Holt, Sylvia, 1889-1945; Howe, Julia Ward, 1819-1910; Hyde, Emily Caroline (Varney); Hyde, William Henry; McClellan, John; McFarlan, Karen N.; McKinley, William, 1843-1901; Medlar, Clara Soule, 1833 or 1834-1902; Mellon, Anna; Monroe, Edward Thayer; Penfield, William Lawrence, 1846-1909; Plummer, John Lincoln; Plummer, Susan Rand (White); Prentier, John H.; Proctor, Edna Dean, 1829-1923; Reed, Grace (Holt), 1874-1937; Richardson, Alice Linden (Bowen), 1854-1948; Richardson, Dorothea (Boyd), 1894-1981; Richardson, Gardner, 1884-1972; Richardson, Rufus B. (Rufus Byam), 1845-1914; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945; Scott, Winfield, 1786-1866; Stoddard, Evelyn; Stowe, Harriet Beecher, 1811-1896; Stuart, Jane S., d. 1916; Tappan, Arthur, 1786-1865; Tappan, Charles; Tappan, Elizabeth; Tappan, Lewis, 1788-1873; Tappan, Susanna (Aspinwall); Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972; Underwood, Samuel; Vereker, Gordon; Vereker, Roxanna Wentworth (Bowen), 1895-; Warren, Fuller, 1905-1973; Washington, George, 1732-1799; Wells, Joseph Collins, 1813-1860; Wentworth, John, 1737-1820; Wentworth, Roxanna Marie (Loomis); White, Henry Bowen; Whittier, John Greenleaf, 1807-1892; Agricultural Society of Windham County (Conn.); American Ambulance Corps (Paris, France); American Antiquarian Society; American Historical Society; American Relief Administration; American School of Classical Studies at Athens; Arnold Manufacturing Company; Arthur Tappan and Company; Bowen and Lyon; Bowen and McNamee; Bowen, Holmes and Company; Brooklyn Heights Seminary; College of William and Mary; Columbia University; Columbia University. School of Law; Commission for Relief in Belgium; Committee on the Centennial Celebration of the Inauguration of George Washington as President of the United States; Congregational Church Building Society; Connecticut Historical Society; Continental Insurance Company of New York; Dartmouth College; Department of Foreign and Domestic Commerce (Washington, DC); Eastman National Business College (Poughkeepsie, N.Y.); Ely, Bowen and McConnell; Ely, Clapp and Bowen; First Ecclesiastical Society of South Woodstock (South Woodstock, Conn.); Fresh Air Fund; Gothic Hall Ladies School (Stamford, Conn.); Indiana University; Judiciary Committee of the Connecticut Legislature; Lawyers' Club (New York, N.Y.); Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.); Miss Porter's School (Farmington, Conn.); New York Genealogical and Biographical Society; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn; Putnam Rotary Club (Putnam, Conn.); Rollins College; Smith, Seaver and Bowen; Southern Railway (U.S.); United States. Legation (Switzerland); Woodstock Academy (Conn.); Yale College (1718-1887); Yale University. Divinity School; Athens (Periféreia Protevoúsis, Greece); Barcelona (Barcelona province, Catalonia, Spain); Belgium; Belmont (Middlesex county, Massachusetts); Berlin (Berlin state, Germany); Bern canton (Switzerland) [canton]; Brookline (Norfolk county, Massachusetts); Brooklyn (New York City, New York state) [borough]; Chaplin (Windham county, Connecticut); Caracas (Distrito Federal, Venezuela); Dudley (Worcester county, Massachusetts); Enfield (Hartford county, Connecticut); Farmington (Hartford county, Connecticut); Florence (Firenze province, Tuscany, Italy); Hague, The (South Holland, Netherlands); Liverpool (Liverpool urban district, Merseyside, England, United Kingdom); Middle East [general region]; Naples (Napoli province, Campania, Italy); New London (New London county, Connecticut); New York City (New York state); Northampton (Hampshire County, Massachusetts); Paris (Ville de Paris department, Île-de-France, France); Persia (Asia) [historical region]; Pomfret (Windham county, Connecticut); Poughkeepsie (Dutchess county, New York state); Putnam (Windham county, Connecticut); Rome (Roma province, Latium, Italy); Roseland Park (Windham county, Connecticut); Stamford (Fairfield county, Connecticut); Toronto (Toronto Metropolitan Area, Ontario, Canada); Troy (Rensselaer county, New York state); Vienna (Vienna state, Austria); Wales (United Kingdom) [country]; Williamsburg (Williamsburg Indep. City, Virginia); Winter Park (Orange county, Florida); Woodstock (Windham county, Connecticut); Worcester (Worcester county, Massachusetts); Tuberculosis; Typhoid fever; United States. History. Civil War, 1861-1865; United States. History. Revolution, 1775-1783; United States. History. War of 1812; Woodstock (Conn.). History; Fourth of July; Bowen Family House (Brooklyn, N.Y.); Roseland Cottage (Woodstock, Conn.); abolitionists; account books; address books; architects; authors; bills (legislative records); black-and-white photographs; books; business (commercial function); businessmen; cabinet photographs; card photographs (photographs); cartes-de-visite (card photographs); clippings (information artifacts); color photographs; contracts; correspondence; deeds; ephemera; estate inventories; family papers; financial records; genealogies; Gothic Revival; invitations; journals (accounts); lawyers; legal documents; letters (correspondence); memorabilia; merchants; military personnel; newspapers; notebooks; notes; obituaries; orators; pamphlets; personal correspondence; personal papers; photograph albums; photographs; photographic materials; poems; politicians; probate records; professional papers; publications; receipts (financial records); ration books; site plans; speeches; swatches; tintypes (prints); travel; wills; writings (document genre)
Collection Inventory
- Papers of the Bowen family of Woodstock, Connecticut, 1774-1986, undated; MS006.01; Family papers (7 file boxes, 1 folio box, 5 oversize folders); Series I, Papers of the Bowen family of Woodstock, Connecticut, 1774-1986, undated (#1.1-5.5, 6.1-6.24, 6.28, 7.1-7.6, FB.1.1-FB.1.2, OB1.3, OB.2.3-OB.2.5, OB.3.7), contains the personal and professional papers of the Bowen family of Woodstock, Connecticut. Included in the series are account books; address books; auctioneer estate catalogs; bills and receipts; biographical and genealogical material; cash books; contracts and agreements; correspondence and notes; financial records; guest books; invitations; journals and notebooks; legal documents; memorabilia; newspapers, clippings, and other printed material; probate records; ration books; site plans; wills; etc. The series also contains materials relating to the Committee on the Centennial Celebration of the Inauguration of George Washington as President of the United States; the Congregational Church Building Society; the First Ecclesiastical Society of South Woodstock, Connecticut; Woodstock Academy in Woodstock, Connecticut; the paintings of artist Clara Soule (1834-1902) at Roseland Cottage in Woodstock, Connecticut; and the purchase of "Dexter Lot" from Samuel Dexter in Woodstock, Connecticut. The series is arranged in twenty subseries. (HGO-02-105-A-E-301; HGO-02-105-A-E-302; HGO-02-105-A-E-101; HGO-02-105-A-E-106)
  - Papers of Clarence Winthrop Bowen (1852-1935), 1886-1915; MS006.01.01; Personal papers (2 file boxes); Subseries A, Papers of Clarence Winthrop Bowen (1852-1935), 1886-1915 (#4.11-4.16, 6.1-6.2), contains 1889 memorabilia (including invitations and banquet material) from Bowen's work as secretary for the Committee on the Centennial Celebration of the Inauguration of George Washington as President of the United States held in New York City, New York, and two of Bowen's published works: Woodstock: An Historical Sketch and "Charter of Connecticut." The "Charter of Connecticut" is inscribed: 'To Edward Augustus Bowen from Clarence Winthrop Bowen, Woodstock, September 27, 1914" and Woodstock [copy 1] is inscribed: "Mary Bowen Holt from Clarence Winthrop Bowen, September 22, 1886.' Also included in the subseries is Bowen's 1915 baccalaureate address delivered at the 222nd annual commencement of the College of William and Mary in Williamsburg, Virginia. The subseries is arranged chronologically by committee material, followed by printed material. (HGO-02-105-A-E-301)
    - Committee on the Centennial Celebration of the Inauguration of George Washington as President of the United States, 1889; MS006.01.01.01; Memorabilia (1 file box); NOTE: See #4.12 and 4.13 for items removed
      - Invitation to reception at the Lawyers Club, New York City, New York, April 29; includes ribbon ties, 1889; MS006.01.01.01.01; NOTE: See #4.12 and 4.13 for items removed (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Invitation to Centennial Celebration, New York City, New York, April 29 - May 1; includes envelope, 1889; MS006.01.01.01.02; NOTE: Item removed from #4.11 NOTE: See #4.13 for related material (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Banquet materials from the Metropolitan Opera House, New York City, New York, April 30, 1889; MS006.01.01.01.03; NOTE: Items removed from #4.11 NOTE: See #4.12 for related material (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Printed material, 1886-1915; MS006.01.01.02; Publications (2 file boxes)
      - Woodstock: An Historical Sketch [softcover], 1886; MS006.01.01.02.01 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Woodstock: An Historical Sketch [hardcover] [copy 1]; includes inscription, 1886; MS006.01.01.02.02 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Woodstock: An Historical Sketch [hardcover] [copy 2], 1886; MS006.01.01.02.03 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - "Charter of Connecticut,"; includes inscription, 1914; MS006.01.01.02.04 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Baccalaureate address delivered at the College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, Virginia, June 10, 1915; MS006.01.01.02.05 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Papers of Edward Augustus Bowen (1847-1926), 1866-1926; MS006.01.02; Personal papers (2 file boxes); Subseries B, Papers of Edward Augustus Bowen (1847-1926), 1866-1926 (#3.1-3.4, 4.2-4.9), contains an account book; two cash books relating to Roseland Cottage in Woodstock, Connecticut; correspondence (including an 1867 letter from Edna Dean Proctor (1829-1923), governess, with a clipping in Russian, #4.2); printed material (including a 1903 letter from judge William L. Penfield, 1846-1909, #4.4); a travel journal describing Bowen's "tug trip" to Liverpool in England, United Kingdom, in the winter of 1880 and his sightseeing excursions in Florence, Rome, and Naples, in Italy; and several wills and drafts of wills. The subseries is arranged alphabetically by record type, and thereunder chronologically. (HGO-02-105-A-E-301)
    - Account book, 1866-1908; MS006.01.02.01 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Cash book re: Roseland Cottage in Woodstock, Connecticut, 1896-1903; MS006.01.02.02 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Cash book re: Roseland Cottage in Woodstock, Connecticut; includes loose items, 1903-1914; MS006.01.02.03 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence; includes 1867 letter from Edna Dean Proctor (1829-1923), and clipping in Russian, 1909-1924; MS006.01.02.04 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Printed material, 1887-1911; MS006.01.02.05; Publications (1 file box)
      - Celebration of Christmas 1887 at 90 Willow Street, Brooklyn, New York; includes inscription: "Edward A. Bowen from Henry C. Bowen", MS006.01.02.05.01 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - "Opening Argument and Reply for the United States," presented to the Arbitration Tribunal of The Hague, Netherlands, November; includes 1903 letter from William L. Penfield (1846-1909), MS006.01.02.05.02 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - My four Great Gandmothers, ca. 1911; MS006.01.02.05.03 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Travel journal re: trip to Europe, 1880-1888; MS006.01.02.06 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Wills, 1918-1922; MS006.01.02.07 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Wills [3 copies], 1926; MS006.01.02.09 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Wills, drafts [6 copies], 1926; MS006.01.02.10 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Wills; includes pages from wills [photocopies], 1918-1919, undated; MS006.01.02.11; NOTE: See #6.18 for item removed [Henry Chandler Bowen family genealogy chart, undated]. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Papers of Edward Eaton Bowen (1815-1887), 1845-1878; MS006.01.03; Personal papers (1 file box); Subseries C, Papers of Edward Eaton Bowen (1815-1887), 1845-1878 (#1.19), contains receipts for the transportation and purchase of goods. (HGO-02-105-A-E-301)
    - Receipts re: transportation and purchase of goods, 1845-1878; MS006.01.03.01 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Papers of Ellen (Holt) Bowen (1834-1903), 1865-1898, undated; MS006.01.04; Personal papers (2 file boxes); Subseries D, Papers of Ellen (Holt) Bowen (1834-1903), 1865-1898, undated (#6.7, 7.2, 7.4), contains two address books and a note describing Bowen's 1865 wedding dress. The subseries is arranged alphabetically by record type, and thereunder chronologically. (HGO-02-105-A-E-301; HGO-02-105-A-E-302)
    - Address book, May, 1898; MS006.01.04.01 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Address book, undated; MS006.01.04.02 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Note re: description of wedding dress, December 28, 1865; MS006.01.04.03 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Papers of Franklin Davis Bowen (1860-1940), MS006.01.05; Personal papers (1 file box); Subseries E, Papers of Franklin Davis Bowen (1860-1940), 1940 (#6.6), contains a 1940 will. (HGO-02-105-A-E-301)
    - Will [photocopy], 1940; MS006.01.05.01 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Papers of George Bowen (1789-1846), 1845; MS006.01.06; Personal papers (1 file box); Subseries F, Papers of George Bowen (1789-1846), 1845 (#1.2), contains financial records regarding tool repairs and the purchase of bolts. (HGO-02-105-A-E-301)
    - Financial records re: tool repairs and purchase of bolts, September -November, 1845; MS006.01.06.01 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Papers of Henry Chandler Bowen (1813-1896), 1833-1896; MS006.01.07; Personal papers (2 file boxes, 1 oversize folder); Subseries G, Papers of Henry Chandler Bowen (1813-1896), 1833-1896 (#1.3-1.18, 2.2-2.3, OB.1.3), is divided into three categories: correspondence, financial records, and legal documents. The correspondence is comprised of a letter to a John McClellan regarding the "hero of Tippecanoe," and correspondence with a John H. Prentier regarding the gift of a handmade quilt from Prentier's mother. The financial records include account books; bills and receipts; and related financial papers. Bowen's account books detail daily business dealings; household expenses; landscaping projects; tuition payments; donations to church and civic activities; building transactions related to Roseland Cottage; etc.; and reflect Bowen's meticulous record keeping activities, which began while in the employment of Arthur Tappan (1786-1865) in New York City, New York. The account book from 1848 to 1871 (#2.2), contains expenditures relating to the construction of Roseland Cottage (pages, 12-15); payments to contractor Edwin Eaton of Chaplin, Connecticut (page 10); and payments to architect Joseph Collins Wells (1814-1860) of Brooklyn, New York (page 18). Also included in the financial records is an embroidered silk swatch with receipt (#1.6); a receipt for trees donated and planted on Woodstock Common in Woodstock, Connecticut (#1.8); tuition bills for Woodstock Academy in Woodstock, Connecticut (#1.9); and material relating to the Congregational Church Building Society (including account books, collection funds, subscriptions, etc.). An 1896 issue of Church-Building Quarterly (#1.13), with a tribute to Bowen (pages 70-77), is also included in the financial records along with two 1896 auctioneer estate catalogs which feature furniture, artwork, and the library collection from the Bowen family property at 90 Willow Street in New York City, New York. The legal documents include a contract for land purchased at 90 Willow Street in Brooklyn, New York; an 1867 will of Samuel Dexter; an1895 will of Bowen; and an 1896 estate inventory for Roseland Cottage in Woodstock, Connecticut. Also included in the legal documents is material related to the purchase of "Dexter Lot" in Woodstock, Connecticut (including a site plan and correspondence with Samuel Dexter, Bowen, and the First Ecclesiastical Society of South Woodstock in South Woodstock, Connecticut). The subseries is arranged alphabetically by record type, then by topic, and thereunder chronologically. (HGO-02-105-A-E-301; HGO-02-105-A-E-106)
    - Correspondence: letter to John McClellan re: hero of Tippecanoe, June 5 [photocopy]; includes letter with transcription from John H. Prentier re: thank you gift, September 14, 1840-1856; MS006.01.07.01 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Financial records, 1833-1896; MS006.01.07.02; Financial records (2 file boxes)
      - Account books; includes account pages [photocopies], 1833-1852; MS006.01.07.02.01 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Account book, 1837-1841; MS006.01.07.02.02 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Account book; includes loose items, 1848-1871; MS006.01.07.02.03 (Box 2, Foler 2)
      - Account book; includes loose items, 1870-1893; MS006.01.07.02.04 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Auctioneer's estate catalogs, 1896; MS006.01.07.02.05 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Congregational Church Building Society, account book re: Society collection funds; includes 1851 account book re: Society subscriptions, 1837-1851; MS006.01.07.02.06 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Congregational Church Building Society, financial records; includes pages from account book [photocopies], 1850-1891; MS006.01.07.02.07 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Congregational Church Building Society, printed material, Church and Building Quarterly; includes tribute to Bowen, 1896; MS006.01.07.02.08 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Household accounts, general accounts; includes embroidered silk swatch and receipt, 1837-1869; MS006.01.07.02.09 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Household accounts, food expenses, 1847-1850; MS006.01.07.02.10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Household account, landscape projects, February-November, 1847-1853; MS006.01.07.02.11 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Household accounts: Woodstock Academy, Woodstock, Connecticut, 1873; MS006.01.07.02.12; NOTE: See also #6.24 for related material (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Receipts for shipping, 1845-1850; MS006.01.07.02.13 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Receipt for highway tax, 1848; MS006.01.07.02.14 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Legal documents, 1853-1896; MS006.01.07.03; Legal documents (1 file box, 1 oversize folder)
      - Abstract of title to land in the City of Brooklyn, Kings County, New York, re: property at 90 Willow Street, 1876, MS006.01.07.03.01; NOTE: See #6.19 for item removed [letter re: key to Roseland Cottage safe]. NOTE: See # OB.1.3 for item removed. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Papers re: "Dexter Lot,"; includes 1867 will of Samuel Dexter, 1853-1867; MS006.01.07.03.02 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Site plan re: tract of land purchased from John McClellan in Woodstock, Connecticut, 1872; MS006.01.07.03.03; NOTE: Item removed from #1.16. (Box OB.1, Folder 3)
      - Probate records; includes 1895 will and 1896 estate inventory [photocopies], 1895-1896; MS006.01.07.03.04 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Papers of Henry Elliot Bowen (1845-1919), undated; MS006.01.08; Personal papers (1 file box); i720Subseries H, Papers of Henry Elliot Bowen (1845-1919), undated (#4.1), contains an undated address book. (HGO-02-105-A-E-301)
    - Address book, undated; MS006.01.08.01 (Box 4, Folder 1)